# **Cian Ronayne**









Dublin, Ireland +353 86 247 1058 cianronayne1@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/cian-ronayne

## **PROFILE**

Digital Marketing Executive with experience in the creation and management of digital marketing strategies and campaigns for Ireland's largest independently owned travel company.

With experience operating multiple digital channels for a range of leading Irish travel agencies; I help build successful digital marketing strategies that increase brand awareness, promote customer engagement and ultimately drive web traffic and conversions.

#### **EDUCATION**

2017 – 2020 | NATIONAL COLLEGE OF IRELAND | BA (Hons) Marketing Practice (2:1)

I have recently completed my degree in Marketing at National College of Ireland. My studies have given me an excellent base of knowledge in a variety of functional business areas such as Marketing Strategy, Project Management, Digital Marketing, Integrated Marketing Communications as well as practical projects in cooperation with real businesses and organisations.

2015 – 2017 | Dublin City University | BA International Relations (Up to second year)

2014 – 2015 | Killester College of Further Education | IT & eBusiness

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Club Travel – HRG Ireland | Digital Marketing Executive | Oct 2018 - Present

- Update and maintain the various brand's websites on a weekly basis.
- Plan and implement "joint marketing" campaigns.
- Maintain various market research reports, drawing from multiple databases. As well as many reports on our own customer's interaction with the brands.
- Copywriting for various social media posts & blogs.

# Tickets.ie | Data Entry Clerk | Sep 2018 – Sep 2018

- Created a user manual for potential clients, to teach them how to use Tickets.ie's online platform.
- Sourced relevant material and content from the platform for use in the manual.
- Edited screenshots of the platform using photoshop, preparing them for the manual.
- Created and maintained multiple spreadsheets to build a map of the platform, and to monitor the progress of the manual itself.

### Two Men And A Truck Chicago | Mover | May 2018 – Aug 2018

- Moved furniture for customers, while providing a high level of customer service.
- Prepared each customer's house for a safe move, to ensure safety for all members is assured.
- Guided customers through paperwork, and informed them of our plan of action.
- Worked as part of a team to provide the best furniture moving service in Chicago, IL.

# The Guinness Storehouse | Retail Assistant | May 2017 – Jun 2017

- Operated the tills in the very busy gift shop, while providing customer services to the storehouse's visitors.
- Provided information on the range of products, to the many customers.
- Replenished the store's shelves and displays at the end of each shift.

# Søstrene Grene | Sales Assistant | Oct 2016 – Apr 2017

- Worked as part of a team to get the store ready for opening day, this required strong organisation skills.
- Maintained the appearance of the store and rotated stock regularly, all while helping customers on the shop floor.
- Operated the tills throughout each work day, providing excellent customer service.

# **INTERESTS**



Rugby



Running



Web Development



Video Games



Mindfulness



Cooking

REFEREES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST